<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Procom 18</string>
    <string name="procom_info1">PROCOM is a two-day event organized every year at the Karachi campus of NUCES since 1998.</string>
    <string name="procom_info2">PROCOM is the yearly flagship event of FAST-NUCES Karachi. It is an educational event which holds competitions in computer science, electrical and business studies.</string>
    <string name="procom_info3">PROCOM hosts participants from all over Pakistan and FAST students themselves. Companies also participate ranging from software houses to career counseling firm to engineering giants. Scholars as well as professionals from various fields attend PROCOM as guests, observers and judges to witness the proficiency of the students.</string>

    <string name="spelling_bee_desc">Consider yourself a walking talking dictionary? Exhausted at people misspelling simple words? Now is the opportunity to showcase your English skills in this competitive Spelling Bee competition. A hit the last time it was organized, this is sure to attract the brightest and smartest talent from across the country to be ready.</string>
    <string name="scrabble_desc">Scrabble, the classic crossword game. You can feel the energy start when you pile on your letters, pick an incredible word, and would like to arrive on a triple-word score. Play the well-known Scrabble amusement the great route as you go up against adversaries no holds barred, for a testing and fun time whether you’re an amateur or a specialist.</string>
    <string name="spoken_words_desc">Spoken word is a form of poetry that often uses alliterated prose or verse and occasionally uses metered verse to express social commentary. Love Urdu poetry? Can you compete others in spoken words? We have the perfect platform for you. Come and participate in the most exciting competition of procom “spoken words”</string>
    <string name="general_knowledge_desc">Consider yourself a genius when it comes to the happening of the modern world? Also, a history buff and can name the premiers of Pakistan? Know the capital of countries? If general knowledge is your forte you really don’t want to miss in this competition and prove your dominance.</string>
    <string name="tug_of_war_desc">A tug-of-war is a sports event in which two teams test their strength by pulling against each other on opposite ends of a rope. Does your group of friends have that strength to pull the opponent? If yes come and participate in the tug of war competition.</string>

    <string name="db_design_desc">The Database design competition is the backbone of PROCOM. In this competition, you must prove your programming and management skills by making a design of database, solve SQL queries and answer some MCQs. But do not forget to keep an eye on the time because it stops for none.</string>
    <string name="sp_desc">Are you a good programmer? And want yourself to be the judge? Then PROCOM provides you a platform, where you can fill up your thirst of programming under “the devilish behavior of time”. This competition is considered as a “KING OF ALL THE PROGRAMMING COMPETITON” because to prove your proficiency you have to show your conceptual and creative thinking skills. In order to win this competition, every team has to clear some rounds and each round has its own flavor. So, fasten up your seats belts and get yourself prepared for the PROCOM “Speed Programming Competition”.</string>
    <string name="sd_desc">So, do you have the proficiency of rectifying the errors in code? Do you possess the knack of eradicating the ambiguities from it? Do you hold the ignition of showcasing your debugging skills along with the coding skills? If you believe in yourself, then grab this moment! This might just be the time to kick-start your debugging journey.</string>
    <string name="mb_desc">Underground mobile developers! Now you have chance to prove yourself; because PROCOM provides you a speedy mobile application development competition. In this competition, participants will be given a task to develop any small mobile application for any development environment but in a tight time constraint. And the teams who will do a great job get a price for that.</string>

    <string name="_desc"></string>
</resources>